Doraemon
kon'na koto ii na, dekitara ii na
Created by
Fujiko. F. Fujio
I like this, wish I could do this
an'na yume kon'na yume ippai arukedo
This dream, that dream, there are that many
min'na min'na min'na kanaete kureru
He'll make all of our dreams come true
Fushigi na pocket de kanaete kureru
With his magical pocket, He'll make all of our dreams come true
sora wo jiyuu ni tobi tai na
I wish I could fly freely in the sky
hai, take-copter
Here, use this Bamboo 'Copter
An, An ,An, tottemo daisuki....
An, An ,An, You're our favorite and beloved...
...Doraemon
An, An ,An, tottemo daisuki....
An, An ,An, You're our favorite and beloved...
...Doraemon
Production:
TV Asahi
Asatsu-DK
Shin-Ei Animation